one million subscribers a youtube milestone i never expected to reach but
100 万订阅者 这是我从未想过会达到的 youtube 里程碑，但这
here's the story of how i got here in 2017 i started the channel with no video
是我在 2017 年如何到达这里的故事 我在没有视频
editing skills and zero expectations i hated the sound of my own voice and have
编辑技能和零期望的情况下开始了这个频道
been told i have the personality of a carrot but i was like screw it i'm going
一个胡萝卜，但我就像搞砸了，我
to try youtube and probably fail and disappoint my mom again in the process i
要去尝试 youtube，可能会失败，并且在这个过程中再次让我妈妈失望我
found there was a need for developer content around angular and firebase so i
发现需要围绕 angular 和 firebase 的开发人员内容，所以我
created some really bad videos that were very useful to this highly specialized
制作了一些非常糟糕的视频对这个高度专业化的观众很有用
audience welcome to angularfirebase you create a new app with the angular cli
欢迎来到 angularfirebase 你用 angular cli 创建一个新的应用程序
then these files are going to be here by default i even remember my very first
然后这些文件将默认在这里我什至记得我的第一条
comment that motivated me to keep pushing forward in the early game the
评论激励我在早期游戏中继续前进
key is to find a specialized unmet need in the market then create the useful
关键是 在市场上找到一个未满足的特殊需求，然后创建观众正在寻找的有用的
educational content that audience is looking for if you're consistent
教育内容，如果你坚持
uploading a new video say once a week that should take you to about 10 000
上传一个新视频，比如每周一次，应该不 在大约一年左右的时间里将您吸引到大约 10 000 个
subscribers in about a year or so but then you'll hit a ceiling by the mid
订阅者，但是您将在
game my video editing skills were much improved to grow further i created
游戏
videos targeted at a wider audience my first real banger was firebase basics my
中期达到上限 我的
philosophy has always been to make the next video better than the last one it
理念一直是让下一个视频比上一个更好
takes a lot of time and experimentation to really optimize the content for what
需要大量时间和实验才能真正优化内容以
your audience is looking for listen to feedback and give the audience what they
满足观众的需求 听取反馈并为观众提供他们
want like i don't show my face in my videos because my handsomeness is
想要的东西，就像我不喜欢 在我的视频中展示我的脸，因为我的英俊会
distracting and it forces me to find useful graphics that actually represent
分散注意力，它迫使我找到有用的图形，实际上代表
what i'm talking about what you don't want to do is copy somebody else not
我在说什么你不想做的是复制别人
only will that eat away at your soul but in order to grow on youtube you really
不仅会侵蚀你的灵魂，而且为了在 youtube 上成长，你真的
need to find the thing that makes you unique to reach 100k subscribers it took
需要找到让你独一无二的东西才能达到 10 万订阅者花了
675 days and 150 uploads the late game is where things get difficult you'll be
675 天和 150 次上传 游戏后期是事情变得困难的地方，你会
extremely burned out at this point and 10xing the road to 100k might seem
非常精疲力尽 尽管公式很简单，但这一点和10xing 通往 100k 的道路似乎
impossible to keep growing though the formula is simple keep uploading and
不可能继续增长继续上传并
keep getting better at this point i started taking a more scientific
不断变得更好 在这一点上，我开始采取更科学的
approach by optimizing two metrics the click-through rating and the watch time
方法，优化点击率和观看时间这两个指标
to optimize clicks you need a good title and thumbnail that's more of an art form
来优化 点击你需要一个好的标题和缩略图，这更像是一种艺术形式
than anything you need to know what your audience wants and how to surprise them
你需要知道你的观众想要什么，以及如何
with something creative for me that comes easy because i also have a lot of
用对我来说有创意的东西来给他们惊喜，这很容易，因为我也有很多
fun and get really excited about every video i create for watch time i have a
乐趣并且真的很兴奋我为观看时间创建的每个视频我都有一个
formula with three ingredients most importantly the content needs to be
包含三个要素的公式最重要的内容需要具有
educational and useful the second ingredient is storytelling there are so
教育性和有用性第二个要素是讲故事有
many interesting stories to tell about the history of software and the people
很多有趣的故事可以讲述软件的历史及其
behind it the final ingredient is humor i can tell jokes that are actually
背后的人最终要素 是幽默吗？我可以讲笑话，这些笑话实际上是
encoded messages of things that i couldn't say otherwise without sounding
对我无法说出来的
like a total dick this has been how to get 1 million youtube subscribers in 100
事情的编码信息 老兄，这就是如何在 100 秒内获得 100 万 youtube 订阅者
seconds and i want to send a huge thank you to everybody who supported my
，我想向多年来支持我频道的每个人表示衷心的感谢，这对我
channel over the years it truly means more to me than you'll ever know i've
来说真的比你所
learned so much met amazing people and have the rare privilege of actually
知道的更重要 很多人遇到了很棒的人，并有幸真正
enjoying what i do for work and now we get to start down the road to 10 million
享受我为工作所做的事情，现在我们开始走向 1000 万
i'm not sure how we'll get there yet but we will get there or die trying thanks
我不知道我们将如何到达那里，但我们会到达那里或死去尝试谢谢
for watching and i will see you in the next one
观看，我会在下一个
[Music]
[音乐]中见到你